starkey.com 2014-12-04

# Starkey.com Privacy Policy & Terms of Use

This site is owned and operated by Starkey Hearing Technologies. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At Starkey Hearing Technologies, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. Rest assured that the information you provide is safeguarded. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

  * Information Starkey Hearing Technologies gathers and tracks 

We gather two types of information about users:

    * Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. We collect this information to customize our features for individual visitors who are Starkey Hearing Technologies customers and to notify customers about updates to our site and products or services. 

    * Information Starkey Hearing Technologies gathers through aggregated tracking is used to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. We collect this information in order to determine how to create the best experience for our customers. We may track search terms entered in our Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users, but this tracking is never associated with an individual user. 

  * Policy amendment 

Starkey Hearing Technologies approaches Internet communications with a strong commitment to individual privacy rights and concerns. As the Internet evolves, our policy will continue to change and develop. We therefore reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time with or without prior notice. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the sites following any changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.

  * Use of personal information 

Starkey Hearing Technologies strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We disclose your information to no third parties unless it is specifically stated otherwise. We may use third party contractors to help us operate our business and the sites or administer activities on our behalf, and may share your personal information with these contractors for those limited purposes. We use your information solely to fulfill services, transact a purchase, and help us improve our website and product offering to you. Notwithstanding any other provision to the contrary, Starkey Hearing Technologies reserves the right to cooperate with local, state and federal officials in any investigation relating to any purported illegal activity(ies) and, when required by law, regulation, legal process or government requests, to disclose any personal information furnished by you or collected by Starkey Hearing Technologies to law enforcement authorities or other relevant or related third parties. 

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Starkey Hearing Technologies or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. By using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Starkey Hearing Technologies abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of data from the European Union. 

  * Children 

Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.

  * Cookies 

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Starkey Hearing Technologies uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site; however, it will help you to participate more actively in some features.

  * Healthcare disclaimer 

The information presented on [starkey.com](http://www.starkey.com/) or [starkeypro.com](http://www.starkeypro.com/) is not intended to be medical advice and should not be relied upon as such. If you suspect a hearing problem, Starkey Hearing Technologies strongly urges you to consult with a qualified physician or hearing professional.

  * Links to other websites and services 

The Starkey Hearing Technologies websites may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These websites have their own policies regarding privacy. You should review those policies when visiting the websites. Starkey Hearing Technologies has no responsibility for linked websites and is not responsible for the content of any such site. Starkey Hearing Technologies  provides these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.

  * Security 

Starkey Hearing Technologies operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers.

  * Contact us 

If you have questions about the Privacy Policy or your experience with any of our sites, please contact us.
